What if I was to tell you
that the current state of your business,
sales, and
marketing wasn't to do with the amount of
effort you're putting in or how much you
want to succeed, it
was quite simply to do with the way you
currently market your
business? A few days ago,
I critiqued three strangers on the
internet.
You guys said it was incredibly helpful.
I've received your applications,
and I'm going to do it.
But whereas it'd be very tempting for me
to go through this list and pick people
that I could show off and seem amazing,
I'm going to be getting
ChatGPT to pick you at random. And
if you would like me to critique
your socials, landing page, website,
YouTube, there's going to be a link in the
description. Click on that,
I'll do it in my next video. Okay,
Megan Banahan.
Let's get into this. First thing
is the Instagram handle,
mb_strengthfitness. I don't rate it.
No one that pays you
is paying mbstrengthfitness.
They're paying Megan.
So first thing,
I'd make this Megan Banahan. If we can,
fine.
Okay, I would take out PT
and online coach here.
The content, the things you talk about,
the way you position yourself
are all going
to allude to people what you do.
"I make fat loss achievable
and sustainable.
Coaching with experience
and understanding." I would just rather
this was a little
bit more specific. If you
were to look back at the last 100 people
that you've
worked with or the last dozen people,
"I help X demographic do
X outcome. DM me 'coach'
or get started by clicking." Okay?
Oh, it looks like you DM'd me before.
Okay, I've just DM'd you
and nothing has happened.
So Megan,
the first thing I'm going to teach you
is how to create a chatbot
automation. So very simply,
you go in here into Manychat.
This isn't very expensive.
Start from scratch.
Now from here,
we're just going to need to create some
kind of trigger.
So you click New Trigger.
User Sends a Message.
Now, we can use AI to recognize intention,
but just say "Detect
specific," and here the word "coach."
Cool. Now Create.
So that's created a trigger.
Anytime someone sends you the word
"coach," boom.
Now the response we're going to want
is an Instagram DM.
Now quickly, for any of you
that haven't used this,
if you get a DM from someone,
it gives you a lot more things
that you can do rather they comment on
your post.
So here,
straight away up in the top corner, "Hey,
thank you so much for sending me
a message." Maybe a little delay,
three seconds.
"Chances are I'm away from my phone right
now.
I will get back to you as soon as I can."
Just something like that.
Now if we go back, Linktree, and again,
we're kind of missing a bit here.
"Get started by clicking." Cool.
Eight-week sustainable fat loss online
program,
gym timetable, free calorie calculator.
Let's see if there
is a data capture on the calorie
calculator. Cool.
So calorie leads, a lot of people
are using this where in essence you get
section
four, put in your email address there. Oh,
no.
So in essence,
I could probably understand why you
haven't got chatbot set up
because we haven't really got anywhere to
send anyone.
Okay, we're going to work on this.
So this is a form squeeze page.
This isn't going to be how I really want
it to be, but going to put it in
here. Let's do another delay.
This time we'll set the delay to 12.
Come back.
Over, done. "PS While I was shooting here,
why don't you work out your calorie
needs using my free calculator?" Add
button, calorie
calculator.
Going to set it to open a website.
There's your ad leads.
Now if we preview this up here, "Hey,
thank you so much for sending me a
message."
Oh, that was quick. "Chances
are I'm away from my phone right now,
but I'll get
back to you as soon as I can." That's just
the waiting 12 seconds.
"PS While you're here,
why don't you work out your calorie needs
using my free
calculator?" Boom. So now, even
if someone's on the other side of the
world, at
least now when people do DM you the word
"coach," chances are you're going to get
their email address out of it.
So that's just a bit of a low-hanging
fruit which I
would have there. Although,
if they know their calories and macros,
they're not
really going to feel too compelled to do
this.
Gym timetable booking app.
Let's have a little look.
Okay, I'm not really sure what this is
or if it needs to be on there.
Let's have a quick look at the old poddy,
Spotify.
Let's have a look if you exist on YouTube.
I was guilty of having a podcast
that I didn't record,
so I can't exactly have a
pop. Recent upload, I like it.
"Looking to lose a few pounds
but don't know where
to start?" I like the title.
Everyone will have their own profile on
the coaching app.
You will have your own workout program.
You'll have your own nutrition plan.
I think we're missing a hook here.
Everyone will have their own profile on
the coaching app.
What coaching app?
Just a little preface to this,
you could be like, "If you're
someone who's looking to lose a few pounds
but you don't know where to start, today
I'm going to talk you through how to use
this coaching app." Hey, and come on, get
the paid version of CapCut,
you old whippersnapper.
Preview, client testimonial. Okay,
we're not really driving much of
a strategy here, but that's okay.
So chatbot automation, first one.
Now this landing page.
"Eight-week sustainable fat loss online
program.
Pop your email below to find out more info
on the next intake." No.
An email address for more info?
You want my contact
details and the ability to contact me
whenever you want for more info?
I don't even know what it
is you're going to give me more info
about.
Okay,
are you going to be kind to me today,
Leadpages? Let's see.
Again, the reason I love Leadpages,
I take it back actually.
So my Mrs, Tay, uses this.
You can see here some of her
Leadpages, 8,000 US dollars,
6% conversion rate.
So she sent 3,500 people there, made 8K.
She can also do split tests where she can
take a landing page, create several
versions of it,
and see from the data which one
is best. Again,
another reason I like Leadpages, there
are loads of templates here.
So let's have a look, see
if there's any for fitness.
Fitness app, fitness membership page,
fitness
program, sales page, health
and fitness opt-in page.
Let's try this one. Oh,
this one looks nice. Let's try this one.
I'm just going to go straight in.
Now I'm going to have to do a bit of work.
Eight-week sustainable fat loss online
program.
The only issue with this
is it sounds like bloody everyone else's.
Okay,
let's call this one MB Strength Fitness.
What's this?
Oh, fantastic. Engagement. Love to see it.
Let's give them some static images.
Not sure I can see any.
Okay, let's try a little Google image,
shall we? Let's just go here.
You know you're pro
when you type in images.google.
MB Strength Fitness. Let's go images.
This will do.
Why is this in a bloody different
language? Oh, bloody hell.
Don't know what's going on there.
Figure it out. Wonderful. Take that.
Thank you very much. Why
are you taking so long to fucking upload,
mate?
There, it's a little bit bigger.
There you go, 350. Looks quite nice,
doesn't it?
Okay, let's have a little look on Mobi.
Oh, we'll have it.
We'll do it in a second.
Okay, so love that.
Maybe we go over to the sections.
Let's put a little widget in.
Maybe a little bit of a text.
Now, what did you say before?
Eight-week sustainable fat loss online
program.
Let's make this a little bit sexier.
"If you give me eight weeks,
I'll give you the best fat loss
results of your life you can sustain
or your money back." Let's maybe go for a
little bit of bold, maybe break this up.
Let's maybe center align this bad boy.
Maybe we go for a little bit What could be
a good font?
Oh, no, Helvetica Bold. All right,
let's have a look.
Normal text, maybe headline one.
Now we're cooking on gas.
Do you know what?
Might keep that as white,
and I might change... Oh, come back.
Actually, ignore that. Let's keep this.
We'll make this bit dark.
Going to take this out of bio.
Maybe we even duplicate this.
Going to bring this bit underneath,
but we'll make it a little bit smaller
because
this is going to be a subheading.
My name is Meg.
My name is Megan,
and I make fat loss cheap and sustainable.
Fantastic. Okay.
All right. What's going on here?
You're probably going to kill me for the
choice of
photos that I've gone for. Now,
this background image, I'm not mad on.
I suppose that image in the background
could be all right for now. Column one.
Let's go back. Column two, section style.
Yes. Get rid of this image, bro.
Here we go.
Get rid of that.
Person on the Skipper merp.
I don't know you.
Lesson,
don't put strangers on your bloody landing
page. Okay. I run...
I kind of needed a bit more info.
Do you know what?
It would've been better
if you give me some actual information on
it,
because I'm not giving you my email
address.
No way,
because you're probably not even going to
send the email through, are you?
Okay, let's think about this.
Let's give this a name.
Five kilos in eight weeks.
Okay.
If you want to drop 5kg in eight weeks,
this system
works and you can start.
Maybe even just that.
If you want to drop 5kg,
this system works.
If you're not happy with the results,
I provide,
only two months.
Okay, what did that lady say? I
was wondering if there was any client
testimonials. Let's just put one in here.
I loved every moment training with Megan.
I came for two months.
I stayed for the result.
I worked hard and achieved the fat loss.
I stayed on as a client because Megan
is awesome.
Loretta. All right.
Join the eight-week challenge.
That's really what the call to action is.
The call to action shouldn't be more
information because no one wants
more information.
No one woke up this morning going, "Oh,
absolutely love some more
information." They got enough information.
Don't know why my headphone's on,
there's no audio to be listening to. Okay.
This eight week is for you want to lose
fat for an
important event. Let's say those
that want to build
strength they keep. Life.
Making these up at this point.
Do you understand?
Those that to build sustainable habits
that don't feel like a chore.
Join the eight-week challenge.
So if we were to preview this now.
I'll get your email marketing emails.
We haven't even got into that bit yet.
Cool.
You send me through to your landing page,
or let's say I click on this from your
page. Granted,
desktop more so from email marketing,
mobile
more so from Instagram. I go, wow, this
is really well put together.
This looks great. Then if we go to mobile.
Maybe this title could be a little bit
smaller, but you get the drift.
If you give me eight weeks,
I'll give you the best fat results of your
life.
Maybe we delete that bit for that.
Actually, tell you what, we'll do
that right
now. To optimize for mobile, we do this.
If you give me eight weeks,
I'll give you the best fat loss results of
your life.
Great photo. My name's Megan.
I make fat loss cheap and sustainable.
If you want to drop 5kg in eight weeks,
this system works. Oh, great.
If you're not happy with the results I
provide in only two months, you get your
money back. Oh, wow. Well,
I've got no reason not to apply.
And again,
I have kind of drafted this up quite
quick.
They might come past this,
go on there a little bit more.
This eight-week challenge
is for those who want to lose fat before
an important
event or occasion. Oh my God, yeah,
I've got my wedding, I've got this party,
I've
got this holiday. Those
that want to build strength they can keep
for life. I do.
I've always been mindful of breaking a
hip.
To build sustainable habits
that don't feel like a chore.
Do you know what?
The last time I got in shape,
it did feel like a chore.
They go to the bottom, they hit the end,
they go, "You son of a bitch, I'm in." The
important thing about this, Megan,
you're doing all the work here, but as it
stands,
you could send 1,000 people to this
and only get two or three
clients. Whereas if you
were to spend what?
10 minutes building out this,
that same amount of traffic could equate
to
80, 90, 100 people.
This doesn't take a long time,
and as you can see,
Leadpages makes this look good for me.
Then very simply, all you'd have to do
is send traffic as hard as you can.
You could set up chatbots,
you could set up stories,
links, hit your email list.
You just go on social media, ba, ba, ba,
ba, bom.
DM me the link, train,
I'll send you some more information.
DM me this, DM me that.
Ideally,
we'd have like a video sales letter,
a video that you create.
Then we can see the unique amount of
visitors and how many of them
are converted.
Then we create variations of that page.
Okay, let's go here.
Let's have a look at your reels.
Profile on the coaching app.
You will have your own workout program.
The Romanian deadlift has to be one of the
most common exercises that people
struggle with. So-
So again, no real hook here.
You're just telling me
that it's something that people
struggle with. Instead, maybe a hook.
If you're someone
that struggles with a Romanian deadlift,
if you're someone that
wants to train your hamstrings,
if you're someone
that wants to develop the back of
your thighs. Again,
we want to use language
that everyone can understand.
The second you say posterior chain,
half the people are leaving.
Let's just run through a couple of simple
coaching cues that's going to help you
become boss at it.
The key part in an RDL movement
is to imagine your hips-
Very common thing
that I see from fitness people
is the first 10 seconds can go. That
is where your reel should begin.
Let's try this one more time.
Deadlift has to be one of the most common
exercises that people struggle with.
So let's just run through a couple of
simple coaching cues that's going to help
you
become boss at-
Delete all of that. And
if you don't believe me, tonight,
delete that,
repost the reel from this bit as a trial
reel.
The key part in an RDL movement-
Then we'll have the two ABs,
your original one, then we chop the fat
off the beginning,
and my one as a trial reel.
You say, the key movement
and the key thing about an RDL movement
Is to imagine your hips as a 90-degree
hinge, and this is-
If this was the first three seconds,
I'd be so much more engaged.
This is a better start to a reel than the
one before, and it might almost seem that
you didn't set it up enough, but trust me,
I think that will work.
It's also known as the hip hinge movement
pattern.
Now,
people normally struggle with this because
they round at the shoulders or they
flex too much at the knee.
If you cut off that first 10 seconds,
this would be better. Let's keep going.
And again, yeah,
we need to change this name. Okay.
What I'm doing now
is I'm actually looking for an outlier.
This one here, 4,000.
Okay, let's have a look. This
is an outlier.
Go and lots of people have been asking me
about the Fit Foods Ready Meals.
So let's go have a look.
So here's the Fit Foods Ready Meals.
The branding is really positioning itself-
At this point, I'm bored, I'm gone.
Because I've stayed for a few seconds to
find out what this video is about, but you
haven't paid me off, so I've gone.
So what I would love
is for you to preface this.
Food label call out. Let's watch that.
Of a health food for fit people with high
protein.
See, look,
even me staying to find out what the
video's about to give you a
critique, I'm bored, I'm gone.
So you to camera should have said
something like,
"There is way too much fearmongering going
on in the space of nutrition." Boom.
Then we cut to this person.
She should be full screen because you just
sat here on
a phone is redundant.
Then we can watch the clip, and again,
if I'm interested
in the fearmongering subject,
I'm going to watch it.
Then we get into your part.
And looks like you haven't reacted to a
piece of content
since, which we should because this one,
70 likes, 35,
15, 22. People want it.
Now Another cry here.
Everyone will have their own profile.
This is you talking people through the
fitness app.
You know where this belongs, don't you?
On your landing page.
Because the reason
that this post has bombed,
although it's only eight hours old,
is Instagram's going to show this to 3,900
people, let's
pretend, and 3,500 people don't care.
But if you'd taken some email addresses
and you'd actually had a chatbot set up
from your profile,
then you might even only have 350 people
on your email list, but
out of them, the majority of them care.
Then when you send them to this video,
100 watch.
And if 100 people watch this video to the
end, maybe 40 or 30 would consider
jumping on it.
So you've put this in the wrong place.
In essence,
this is like you opening your window
and shouting
out. Not you, because you're engaged.
I'm happy for you, but everyone else,
open your window.
"Anyone fancy a shag?" Now, no one
is probably going to say,
"Yes." Whereas,
if you had given yourself an hour,
downloaded a
dating app, swiped 150 times,
you would've got four matches.
Two of them are available for a drink
tonight.
You pick your favorite one who lives
closest. Boom, you go out.
Much more likely to do it. There
are stages in which you go in to get the
desired
outcome in which you need.
You've tried to skip a few steps.
You are shouting for a shag out the
window.
Copyright, someone put that on a T-shirt.
No email list, no landing page, no DM
automations. You're doing the work,
you're doing the posts.
If you fix those things,
I see more success from the same amount of
effort,
which is the exciting thing
that you should all get very,
very excited about.
Same amount of work,
way more because of it.
Okay, back to ChatGPT. Okay, please pick
someone else at random.
Preferentially not a fitness
person.
You should critique Astra's website. Oh,
it says social.
Cor, you would think AI would know.
Oof, it's quite difficult to read that.
Okay.
I like the font.
I don't like the fact this is a website.
I haven't even looked at your socials yet.
One of my gripes is I've landed here.
There's a lot for me to take in in one go.
I can't really read this text.
"Your full stack retention partner."
Okay. Home, services, training. All right,
let's do this.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Six things to
click. Okay. It's not terrible.
I like the colors.
The color palette is absolutely fantastic.
Let's go to the socials.
Locorum Astra. Locorum Astra. Oh,
Locorum Astra?
Is Astra your first name? Okay,
I don't know if I would like your name to
be first,
but okay. Building Locorum Media.
Now,
I don't think this needs to be tagged
if it is just a
dead page. Just put it in. £10 million
plus generated for clients.
I'm going to throw it out there,
hate to be that
person. I don't believe you. Now, even
if you can, maybe make it a bit more
believable.
Maybe dumb it down a little bit.
Not just literally saying that.
As far as being an asshole,
you've got 86 followers.
I come on to your page,
you're telling me you've made 10 mil for
your clients.
I'm just not sure I believe that yet.
We can build authority as we go along.
But anyway, let's have a look.
Retention growth partners.
Think of us as your secret source behind
boosting your
brand's long-term growth and success.
We-
This needs to be better lit.
It's very dark.
Now, I'm not sure if...
What's this filmed on?
Maybe a high spec camera.
He's probably using an ND filter inside,
but-
Craft innovative, data-informed,
and custom-
This needs a light. You know, mate,
I'm not even being funny.
Whoever your videographer
is could have just done that, and yeah,
not well lit
enough, but-
... focused retention strategies.
It's designed to elevate your brand,
increase customer lifetime value,
and reduce
churn.
Who's this for?
So I'm scrolling on my Insta.
Hey, I'm Astra,
the co-founder of Locorum Media.
We're your retention growth partners.
Retention growth partner. Now,
I'm not being funny,
I'm not sure what that is.
Retention growth partners.
Think of us as your secret source behind
boosting your brand's long-term growth and
success. We craft innovative,
data-informed,
and customer-focused retention
strategies.
It's designed to elevate your brand,
increase customer life-
There's a lot of corporate waffle going on
right now.
Keep in mind, I've got several businesses.
If you're good and you're going to give me
return on investment, I want to give you
my money, but there's just a lot of jargon
... lifetime value, and reduce churn,
as well as building beaut-
Look, I'm not
being funny,
but this sounds a little bit like
something you would overhear on
someone on the phone in a Soho house.
"Oh, yeah, innovative, reduce the churn."
Not taking the piss.
I'd just love you to be real,
and maybe even you sat at a seat
with a mic and going,
"Your clients leave you after three
months, and that's a
problem. But don't worry,
we're here to fix it." Then you could go
into reasons why
people lose clients,
why they don't retain,
some of the pitfalls they fall
into. Then at the end, you'd be like,
"My name's Astra, and I help people retain
their clients.
If you want to know more information,
click."
... Playbook series,
where I break down everything you need to
build a
high-converting email
and retention strategy from scratch.
No offense, I'm bored.
Hey.
Welcome to episode one of the Email
and Retention Playbook series.
Series? Go on.
Where I break down everything you need to
build a high-converting email and
retention strategy from scratch.
So the first step in any successful email
and retention marketing strategy is
building a strong list.
Everyone's gone. Everyone's already gone.
Best way to do this
is a high-converting website pop-ups.
Let's restructure this.
If you have a website
that doesn't have a pop-up, you are
leaving email addresses on the table,
and I'm going to explain why.
Or another one.
Out of every 100 people who visit your
website, you should be getting 20 email
addresses, and if you're not,
it's because you're failing to do the one
thing that
successful businesses do, and that
is creating an innovative form of pop-up.
Research has shown that websites
that use a pop-up get to capture more data
and
build their... Okay, ironically,
in your caption here, you've said, "Here
are the key elements of a high-converting
pop-up.
One,
a strong hook." Let's start this video
again
... one of the Email
and Retention Playbook series,
where I break down everything
you need to build a high-
Welcome to episode one.
You do not have a hook in your own
videos.
So you're telling people how they can
capture more attention
by using a hook for their pop-up,
but you don't use a hook in your outbound
social media content
... converting email
and retention strategy from scratch.
So the first step in any-
Now, whilst I'm saying this,
and I am picking you apart,
I love the demeanor,
I love the energy, I love the confidence.
You look relatively young,
and the fact that you're
just being a boss,
you're grabbing the mic,
you're getting out there,
kudos to you.
So even though it can sound like I'm
criticizing you, and dare I say
it, absolutely not insinuating
that I'm mansplaining,
but there is so much you're doing right.
Just had to give you the credit for
that before we go any further
... successful email
and retention marketing strategy
is building a strong list.
The-
Perfect pronunciation,
the way you're speaking,
easy to understand Like it.
Best way to do this
is a high-converting website pop-up.
So this, although it can feel
is your payoff, is actually your hook, or
it's part of your setup.
So you've tried to allude to some things
before, and then
you've presented the pop-up.
But you should be using the pop-up.
Even to begin with, why is it
that some websites get loads of email
addresses while
others don't?
It's because of this one very thing.
You could drag it out.
And if people would only implement this
thing, they could get way more customers
from the exact same amount of traffic.
And that thing is a website pop-up.
The key elements of a high-converting
pop-up. One, a strong hook.
Give visitors a compelling reason to
subscribe.
Options include a discount,
like get 10% off your first order,
exclusive
access-
And these bits of information
are really good.
I like the piece of content.
You're telling people about a strong hook.
You need a bloody strong hook.
"Your discount strategy is hurting you."
Good hook. So one day ago. Oh,
look at this frequency.
"Welcome to— Your discount strategy-
14 hours ago, one day ago. Look at
that content frequency.
Here is, "Your discount strategy
is hurting you.
Discounts aren't a retention strategy."
Okay. This. Great. Love it.
Sure,
a promo can get your customers through the
door, but if you train them to
wait for sales,
you're creating an environment where
they're never going to
purchase full price from your brand.
So here's what to do instead.
Create exclusive early access to your
promos, so VIP perks over-
Do like this.
Here are three websites
that I like to go for inspiration for
email design and
copywriting when my-
I like this.
You have a formula for success on the
table.
Now, one thing. With your profile picture,
no black and white, no bueno.
This ain't Schindler's List. All right?
Never seen a black
and white thumbnail do well.
Nine out of 10 times,
never seen a black and white.
It just seems a bit malaise, a bit sad.
Just a bit sad.
Okay. Where's your outlier? Oh,
here they are.
Email marketing is something that
is arguably more important than
social media.
Mm-hmm.
At the moment, for a long time,
it's been like 50% of our revenue.
Mm-hmm.
And as standard,
I think it should be like, I think-
She suffers from the same issue
that I suffer with, and that
is saying the word
"like" way too much.
Industry standard is like 20, and I meet-
Again, not enough lighting here.
You've got some reviews out there.
Watching me is my anxiety.
Okay. This Gen Z boss thing.
Wow. First-
I do like the Gen Z boss concept
... priority is always a coffee
and checking through my emails.
I get ready early as I've usually got
calls, so I have to look at least partly
presentable. I then make breakfast
and continue with some work.
I will-
Okay. There's a lot of potential here.
A lot of potential.
I kind of want to know. Ugh,
so many websites. Okay.
One thing I would love on this page
is just for us to
bring maybe the text in a little bit.
It looks amazing. It looks amazing.
It's aesthetic as.
I just think the readability
is quite difficult.
I would love to know, how big
is this team? Is it a team?
Straight away, I want to know, is it you?
If it is you on your own, that's fine.
Oh, eat my words. Okay,
you're going to think I'm crazy.
Three of your young guns. I would love,
I would just love
this, okay? When I land on your website,
there's a video, and it's you.
You go, "Hi, I'm Astra. I'm Ellie. Cut.
And I'm George.
And I know that we can seem very young,
but if you can just park our age to the
side,
let us tell you about some of the results
that we've got for our clients."
Because that's really the elephant in the
room.
When you say there
that you've done 10 million in this,
10 million in that, it's
hard to believe you because you're young.
And that's me just being real for a
second.
It's crazy that someone saying the exact
same thing as you that looks a bit older
and weathered is just a bit more
believable. Now, I love this.
We got through some flow. This is Klaviyo,
I believe.
Nice deliverability, nice case studies,
nice marketing performance.
This is great.
But what I would love isn't just the rev
that the business is
generating, but the impact you've made.
And think about this.
So I did a video the other day.
It wasn't the other day,
it's probably quite far
back. How I automated a 5K a day business,
right?
It may seem underwhelming for me to say
5,000 US dollars a day, but that is
not only aspirable for a huge amount of
people, it's believable.
If I say I make 100K a day,
and I know you don't, you're full of shit.
Didn't Steven Bartlett get in a bit of hot
water recently for where he
valued his business? But it
was more so the business
that he sold his business to's
value.
In a world where a lot of people fluff
their numbers quite a
bit to make it seem like they're more
important than they are, this just
seems kind of vague. Revenue generated.
90% increase in repeat purchases.
I'm sorry, it's just not believable.
Rewind to 2015. I was running a
pretty good face-to-face PT business.
I went to get a phone.
But it was with Apple,
you could finance the iPhone 12 months
interest free.
So even though I had the money, I
was like, "Yeah, fine.
Split the payments up.
Cool." And when he asked me how much I
earned as a PT, I shaved, I think 20,000
pounds off my annual salary because I
wanted him to believe me.
Now,
I think we need smaller specific numbers
here, because anyone can write a
number, anyone can write screenshots.
You could be in the back end of someone
else's email marketing campaign.
And I actually think the impressive thing
here is, I'm going to go out on a limb,
it's not the screenshots, it's this.
Three young people, aspirational, probably
competent. This is your selling point.
This is cool.
I would love to see more of you guys.
This, if you're going to use it as a page,
you need some stuff here. LinkedIn.
Let's have a look.
I suppose you're on the right trajectory.
You've already started doing this kind of
stuff.
Email and retention for e-commerce brands.
I would still love a sentence,
"I help X businesses do X." Oh,
you tried to
connect. Do you know what? Have it. Okay.
Do you know what your homework is, Astra?
I would love you to create a YouTube video
where you would
walk through,
similar to what I'm doing now.
Maybe take one of your past customers,
create a YouTube video, explain
exactly the processes you went through to
get them to increase their revenue and
their retention.
Then you're going to go onto a website
called Opus Pro, and on
Opus Pro,
you can chuck in any YouTube video,
and it will give you clips.
So for instance, here's the video
that I did with Lucas and
that Simon Scrib, and
AI goes through, chop, chop, chop, chop,
chop, chop, chop, and chops it up.
Like people talk about the pandemic,
loved it. Sounds bad.
The pandemic was the best time of my life.
Not a care in the world.
That's a fun video
if you haven't watched it.
It should be the one before this one.
So Astra, that would be the advice
that I would give you.
Okay,
we've got enough time for a fast fire.
But keep doing what you're doing.
It's very impressive what you're doing.
I just need a bit more believability.
But there's no way
that you turn up on social media
and speak well like this-
Welcome to episode one of the email- Hey,
I'm Astra, the co-founder of Licorice
Media. We-
I want you to really think about the very
first thing you say, and I want it to be
pungent, offensive, in my face.
Your email marketing sucks.
You're sending emails wrong.
Your website is not optimized for this.
I want you to stab me, stab me,
twist the knife, take it out, give
me the solution. There's your homework.
This is for opening envelopes
and burglars.
I'm a high testosterone dude, right?
I'm just like anyone else,
where I lay in bed
and sometimes think about getting
burgled, and I think, "Do you know what?
Try it." I've been trained in jujitsu for
nearly 10 years, just waiting for the
moment. I wouldn't kill him or her.
Never know.
But you could be getting one of them in
the back of the leg.
If you'd like me to critique your page,
there'll be a link for it in the
description.
Thank you very much for watching this far.
Hope you enjoyed the video